A Guide to the WLR Foods digital records, 1948-2002 (bulk 1984-2000)
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Correspondence, 1988-1991, (8 items)
  - Inter-Office Corres. To Gene Misner from Steve Bolden, September 26 1988
  - Letter to WLR from Johnson & Higgins, October 5 1988
  - Letter from Wampler-Longacre to Stephen Custer, February 16 1989
  - Letter to Mr. Delbert Seitz concerning a "revolving line of credit", April 3 1990
  - Letter to William D. Wampler from James L. Keeler concerning merger, April 9 1990
  - Letter to Board of Directors from KPMG Peat Marwick, December 3 1991
  - Letter from Dot Wampler-Landen, undated